The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
According to Duanmu Ji,
this should be the gate to the first trial.
I have no way back...
I can only move forward.
Come out !
Master, I'm here !
Who do you want me to kill ?
Where are they ?
How many are there ?
Go in.
Are you crazy !?
You want me to go in there !?
Who knows what's inside ?
I won't.
Absolutely not !
At worst,
we will just die here together.
A soul ?
I mustn't fall for it.
W...wait !
Fine, I'll go in...
It's yours when you come back.
Life is so unfair !
Master...
the soul...
Fire...
Metal...
It seems these trials are related to the 5 elements.
I only know the Earth Escape Technique.
Only in the Earth trial
will I have an advantage.
I should just go in a few more times
and properly fleece that fiend !
As long as I keep devouring souls,
I'll be able to deal with him one day.
Master, another one ?
Thank you Master !
Your servant Xu Liguo is willing to serve you tirelessly
through all dangers and hardships !
Master...
I already gave you all I had,
you should've saved them.
Go back in.
What is this thing ?
Bastard, stop it !
I'll go, I'll go !
Found it !
This fiend
is working me to death !
Even if I haven't done anything, I’m still working hard !
First Trial: Earth
Land of the Ancient God
It looks like
in order to clear this trial
I need to reach that gate.
It's coming...
This is the end !
I should have just fought him to the death !
I should've died like a man...
Earth Escape !
Master's plan is brilliant !
With the Earth Escape Technique in this Earth trial
you're like a fish in water !
You're noisy.
Master, I'm not done !
Give me another soul !
Heavens bless me !
Master is a living saint !
Since we have the Earth Escape Technique,
this Earth trial won't hurt me like the others.
Master,
I braved all dangers
to find this place for you !
Could I maybe...
get another reward ?
This is bad !
This tornado
is made of beasts !
Break !
Something's wrong.
It's time for me to shine !
Come back !
They're calling for backup !?
Where is their honor ?
We're done for...
We can't fight them !
We can't run away...
This black tower is strange.
Could it be...
I must try.
Wh...What...
What are you doing ?
You're crazy !
Good,
it's as I suspected.
This black tower
has a restriction to ward off the beasts.
I hope this fiend gets trapped here forever.
When you die,
I'll devour you.
Xu Liguo.
Your servant is here !
W...what ?
Why is he smiling ?
He...
is about to sacrifice me...?
Eat this.
What ?
So it really is
my last meal...
Whatever !
I'd rather die stuffed !
Try flying over that tornado.
Don't fly too high.
Okay...
Watch me open a path
for you, Master !
I never would have thought
that you would set me free one day !
So there's also a restriction in the sky.
It's a shame I lost my devil...
Master !
There's a restriction in the sky
that prevents cheating.
But...
when I was in the tornado
I swallowed a bunch of these beasts.
Those beasts see me like mice see a cat,
they didn't even try to fight !
Serves them right for bullying you !
I, Xu Liguo,
have avenged you, Master.
They didn't attack you ?
I mean... A little bit...
but for each hit I take, I devour 2 of them.
When you devoured their souls
were they weak ?
Huh ?
Weird...
I think you're right.
Individually, these beasts are weak.
In that case,
if I tame a powerful one
I should be able to control a tornado.
Spit out half of the souls
you just devoured.
What ?
Master, I promise I'm not lying.
They're all here.
What the hell is he doing ?
As expected,
these souls are all compatible with each other.
They're all copies of the same soul.
It's the perfect material.
He...
He's creating a devil !
No way,
I need to quickly absorb
the 250 souls I devoured.
Otherwise, if this new devil is stronger than me
the fiend will surely feed me to him !
Xu Liguo
Yes !
Catch more souls.
300 ?
Go !
I'll go...
I did it.
The weak group together
and eventually form a tornado.
The powerful beast I created
attracts weaker beasts
to make a similar tornado.
Th...this...
Who did this ?
The tornado was poisoned to death.
That's the work of the Soul Formation poison cultivator,
Hunchback Meng.
Damn it...
The more I kill, the more come.
Tell me Li Tian,
how about we have some fun together ?
Mere Core Formation and Nascent Soul beasts...
So what if more of you are here ?
I haven't had this much fun killing in years.
Keep coming !
Count the specks of time
floating down gently.
The carving knife in your hands etches out destiny.
Forever lock away the scars
of this mortal life.
This fleeting youth is a thing of the past.
The flying bird could not escape the twilight
that fills the sky with a myriad of colors.
The night-blooming flower cannot drink
the crystalization of the golden wind and the jade dew.
I will ask the heavens who exactly
sliced open this world
to let the rain fall in.
I will refine the world
to make our palm lines say
that we will live forever.
Walking off the beaten path
through heaven and earth.
Before returning to dust,
I will refine this mortal body.
The left shore is the joyous laughter
that can brighten up a thousand years of sadness.
The right shore is an eternal silence
lingering under the candlelight.
To overturn this fate,
I will walk against the heavens.
I will even gather the clouds
to illuminate the sky for you.
All this sadness was not meaningless.
How many lives and deaths
have passed in the blink of an eye ?
I vow to break
this chess game of fate.